HR ASSISTANT- RECRUITING Summary

Self-motivated and organized professional with a strong background in marketing, information systems, and HR/Recruitment policies. Skilled communicator, who works positively, and excels in relationship building with established rapport in culturally diverse groups and businesses. Experienced supervisor and trainer with successful conflict resolution. Innovative, enthusiastic, and uncompromising work ethic.

Highlights

- Microsoft Excel, Word, Outlook, PowerPoint
- SAP HANA, SQL HTML, Business Objects
- Social Media /Advertisement/Marketing
- Customer Service/Community outreach
- Strong writing and communication
- Able to handle sensitive information effectively
- Systems Thinking/Design analytics
- HIPAA/HR/Recruitment/Compliance policies
- ERP, HRIS tools: Meditech, Midas
- HealthcareSource- Position/Requisition/Performance
- MaxHire (Bullhorn) Recruiting software ATS
- Medefis- Vendor Management System
- HRIS- Proficient in ADP Enterprise
- PC and Mac Proficient

Associations

Association of Women in Business CSUC 2007

American Marketing Association CSUC 2011

Experience

HR Assistant- Recruiting

April 2014 to Current Transdevna i1/4 Baltimore, MD

- Conducts all recruitment employment verifications to ensure timely onboarding for monthly orientation.
- Developed creative recruiting strategies that met anticipated staffing needs.
- Communicated duties, compensation, working conditions and application status to inquiring job applicants.
- Created new employee self-evaluation forms that focused on employee performance, competencies, engagement and development.
- Coordinates and tracks the status of employees in the recruiting process, including stages of requisition.
- Maintains accurate reports for employee physicals, background checks, special certifications and testing.
- Maintains job descriptions while continuously updating applicant tracking systems of candidate activity.
- Facilitates enrollment and audits for programs such as Educational Assistance and Loan Forgiveness.
- Acts as main point of contact for managers/employment agencies regarding temporary staffing needs.
- Processed for new registry, contract and clinical traveler staff to ensure compliance for license renewals.
- Attends career fairs/mock interviews per community outreach to attract qualified applicants.
- Processes onboarding paperwork and recruits for internships, job shadows, ROP, and HERO programs.

Perinatal Clerk

November 2013 to April 2014 Enloe Medical Center i1/4 Chico, CA

- Accurately completes and submits birth certificates and paternity paperwork to county.
- Reviews and submits to medical records to ensure proper coding of clinical information.
- High complexity unit scheduler, utilizing the Community Wide Scheduling system.
- Serves as a liaison between hospital department staff and physician offices.
- Collects all required demographic, insurance, financial and clinical data necessary to register patients.

Guest Service Representative

January 2013 to April 2014 Columbus Hospitality i1/4 Columbus, OH

- Act as manager on duty for all adult and junior volunteers within the hospital.
- Responsible for the data analytics of hospital traffic to assist in the assignment of volunteer schedules.
- Train volunteers on hospital wide computer software system, Meditech.
- Facilitate main lobby traffic by assisting all visitors to appropriate departments.
- Oversaw management of the Enloe Medical Center's Gift Shop.

Account Director

August 2012 to November 2012 Rightpoint il/4 Oakland, CA

- Maintained a weekly scheduled point of contact to provide strong relationships with local businesses.
- Sold social media packages and assisted with insights to strategic marketing layouts for new advertising.
- Responsible for all sale/recruitment of local print advertising for Synthesis Weekly publication.

Third Key Manager

November 2009 to July 2012 Claire's Boutique i1/4 City, STATE

Trained and supervised sales associates on maintenance of average dollar sales and units per transaction.

Collaborated between corporate personnel in central California territories to achieve operational goals.

Regional Clinical Analyst- Intern

November 2011 to June 2012 Novasyte LLC i1/4 City, STATE

- Developed relationships with top sales talent in Northeast territory, placing consistent cold calls/emails.
- Scout potential talent through job boards, social media, and interoffice system, Maxhire.
- Kept contact with Account Executives to ensure scouting requirements were aligned with client needs.
- Cultivated the Tiered Internship Program, in which entry interns, managed under regional analysts, work towards a tiered level status of employment, encouraging motivation, involvement, and ownership.

Education

MBA: Management Information Systems, 2014 California State University, Chico it/4 City, State GPA: GPA: 3.642

GPA: 3.642

Bachelors of Business Administration : Marketing , 2012 California State University $i^1\!/_4$ City , State Skills

Customer service, HRIS, HR, marketing, personnel, policies, print advertising, processes, coding, recruitment, sales, scheduling, staffing, insurance, financial, strategic marketing, vendor management